when you stare into the future what
comes to your mind will you be happy and
relaxed or will you be working twice as
hard even in your old years the
decisions you make today will shape your
tomorrow time as we know is fast spent
as the years go by will you still have
the strength to work as hard as you do
now will you still be able to afford a
comfortable living the list of what we
need to take care of today is equally
long and tedious medical bills education
food clothing shelter You Name It We are
too busy taking care of today that we
forget that our future needs to be
catered to get yourself a pro investor
plus policy and enjoy peace tomorrow
rest assured that should anything happen
to you your loved ones will be
financially secured with this plan you
can grow wealth for the people that
depend on you with an option of getting
some money every three years should you
need it how it works all you need to do
is make regular contributions either
monthly quarterly half yearly or yearly
as you are able to a minimum of 20 of
the regular contribution is utilized
towards the above benefits whilst a
maximum of 80 percent is allocated to
investment
just like that little by little you
would have made enough to take care of
yourself and your loved ones it takes
courage to make the decision to invest
in your future make that decision today
contact us today email customer care
prudential.ug or call Plus
256-312-251-400 or speak to any of the
Prudential agents for more information
let's face life together tulinawe
Prudential is regulated by the insurance
regulatory authority of Uganda